{
  "posts": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "title": "json-server",
      "author": "typicode"
    }
  ],
  "comments": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "body": "some comment",
      "postId": 1
    }
  ],
  "profile": {
    "name": "typicode"
  },
  "menu": {
    "menuA": [
      {
        "category": "categoryA",
        "question": "questionA",
        "ans": "answerA",
        "child": [
          {
            "child_category": "categoryA-1",
            "child_question": "Achild_questionA-1",
            "child_answer": "child_answerA-1"
          },
          {
            "child_category": "categoryA-2",
            "child_question": "child_questionA-2",
            "child_answer": "child_answerA-2"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "category": "categoryB",
        "question": "questionB",
        "ans": "answerB",
        "child": [
          {
            "child_category": "categoryB-1",
            "child_question": "child_questionB-1",
            "child_answer": "child_answerB-1"
          },
          {
            "child_category": "categoryB-2",
            "child_question": "child questionB-2",
            "child_answer": "child_answerB-2"
          }
        ]
      }
    ],
    "menuB": [
      {
        "category": "categoryA",
        "question": "questionA",
        "ans": "answerA",
        "child": [
          {
            "child_category": "categoryA-1",
            "child_question": "child_questionA-1",
            "child_answer": "child_answerA-1"
          },
          {
            "child_category": "categoryA-2",
            "child_question": "child_questionA-2",
            "child_answer": "child_answerA-2"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "category": "categoryB",
        "question": "questionB",
        "ans": "answerB",
        "child": [
          {
            "child_category": "categoryB-1",
            "child_question": "child_questionB-1",
            "child_answer": "child_answerB-1"
          },
          {
            "child_category": "categoryB-2",
            "child_question": "child questionB-2",
            "child_answer": "child_answerB-2"
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  "dropdown": {
    "parentCategory": [
      {
        "name": "menuA"
      },
      {
        "name": "menuB"
      },
      {
        "name": "menuC"
      }
    ],
    "category": [
      {
        "name": "categoryA"
      },
      {
        "name": "categoryB"
      },
      {
        "name": "categoryC"
      }
    ],
    "childCategory": [
      {
        "name": "categoryA-1"
      },
      {
        "name": "categoryA-2"
      },
      {
        "name": "categoryA-3"
      },
      {
        "name": "categoryB-1"
      },
      {
        "name": "categoryB-2"
      },
      {
        "name": "categoryB-3"
      }
    ]
  },
  "table": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "order": 1,
      "title": "標題",
      "status": "未審核通過",
      "startDate": "2021-07-03",
      "endDate": "2021-07-05"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "order": 2,
      "title": "標題",
      "status": "未審核通過",
      "startDate": "2021-07-03",
      "endDate": "2021-07-05"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "order": 3,
      "title": "標題",
      "status": "未審核通過",
      "startDate": "2021-07-03",
      "endDate": "2021-07-05"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "order": 4,
      "title": "標題",
      "status": "未審核通過",
      "startDate": "2021-07-03",
      "endDate": "2021-07-05"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "order": 5,
      "title": "標題",
      "status": "未審核通過",
      "startDate": "2021-07-03",
      "endDate": "2021-07-05"
    }
  ],
  "question": [
    {
      "category": "categoryA-1",
      "question": "問題Axxxxxx",
      "answer": "答案xxxxxx"
    },
    {
      "category": "categoryA-2",
      "question": "問題Bxxxxxx",
      "answer": "答案xxxxxx"
    },
    {
      "category": "categoryA-3",
      "question": "問題Cxxxxxx",
      "answer": "答案xxxxxx"
    },
    {
      "category": "categoryB-1",
      "question": "問題Dxxxxxx",
      "answer": "答案xxxxxx"
    },
    {
      "category": "categoryB-2",
      "question": "問題Exxxxxx",
      "answer": "答案xxxxxx"
    },
    {
      "category": "categoryB-3",
      "question": "問題Fxxxxxx",
      "answer": "答案xxxxxx"
    }
  ]
}
